[
  {
    "question": "विलोम शब्द चुनें",
    "word": "बालक",
    "correctAnswer": "बालिका",
    "wrongAnswer1": "कन्या",
    "wrongAnswer2": "बालौ"
  },
  {
    "question": "विलोम शब्द चुनें",
    "word": "प्रसन्न",
    "correctAnswer": "उदास",
    "wrongAnswer1": "उत्तेजित",
    "wrongAnswer2": "रुष्ट"
  },
  {
    "question": "विलोम शब्द चुनें",
    "word": "शीतल",
    "correctAnswer": "उष्ण",
    "wrongAnswer1": "शीत",
    "wrongAnswer2": "शिव"
  },
  {
    "question": "विलोम शब्द चुनें",
    "word": "मृत्यु",
    "correctAnswer": "जीवन",
    "wrongAnswer1": "नरक",
    "wrongAnswer2": "शान्ति"
  },
  {
    "question": "विलोम शब्द चुनें",
    "word": "जल",
    "correctAnswer": "अग्नि",
    "wrongAnswer1": "पृथ्वी",
    "wrongAnswer2": "गगन"
  },

  {
    "question": "अनुलोम शब्द चुनें",
    "word": "राम",
    "correctAnswer": "मार",
    "wrongAnswer1": "रम",
    "wrongAnswer2": "मर"
  },
  {
    "question": "अनुलोम शब्द चुनें",
    "word": "निर्मल",
    "correctAnswer": "लर्मिन",
    "wrongAnswer1": "निर्मा",
    "wrongAnswer2": "र्मलि"
  },
  {
    "question": "अनुलोम शब्द चुनें",
    "word": "धर्म",
    "correctAnswer": "मर्हद",
    "wrongAnswer1": "अधर्म",
    "wrongAnswer2": "मधुर"
  },
  {
    "question": "अनुलोम शब्द चुनें",
    "word": "गोपाल",
    "correctAnswer": "लापक",
    "wrongAnswer1": "पालग",
    "wrongAnswer2": "गपोल"
  },
  {
    "question": "अनुलोम शब्द चुनें",
    "word": "कृष्ण",
    "correctAnswer": "णर्श्क",
    "wrongAnswer1": "शुक्न",
    "wrongAnswer2": "न्श्कर"
  },

  {
    "question": "का विपरीत लिंग चुनें",
    "word": "कन्या",
    "correctAnswer": "बालक",
    "wrongAnswer1": "नारी",
    "wrongAnswer2": "पुत्री"
  },
  {
    "question": "का विपरीत लिंग चुनें",
    "word": "नारी",
    "correctAnswer": "पुरुष",
    "wrongAnswer1": "स्त्री",
    "wrongAnswer2": "बालिका"
  },
  {
    "question": "का विपरीत लिंग चुनें",
    "word": "स्त्री",
    "correctAnswer": "पुंस",
    "wrongAnswer1": "कन्या",
    "wrongAnswer2": "मित्र"
  },
  {
    "question": "का विपरीत लिंग चुनें",
    "word": "बालिका",
    "correctAnswer": "बालक",
    "wrongAnswer1": "नारी",
    "wrongAnswer2": "स्त्री"
  },
  {
    "question": "का विपरीत लिंग चुनें",
    "word": "पुरुष",
    "correctAnswer": "स्त्री",
    "wrongAnswer1": "बालक",
    "wrongAnswer2": "नारी"
  },

  {
    "question": "का बहुवचन चुनें",
    "word": "फलम्",
    "correctAnswer": "फलानि",
    "wrongAnswer1": "फला",
    "wrongAnswer2": "फलं"
  },
  {
    "question": "का बहुवचन चुनें",
    "word": "पत्रम्",
    "correctAnswer": "पत्राणि",
    "wrongAnswer1": "पत्राः",
    "wrongAnswer2": "पत्रे"
  },
  {
    "question": "का बहुवचन चुनें",
    "word": "फलम्",
    "correctAnswer": "फलानि",
    "wrongAnswer1": "फलम्",
    "wrongAnswer2": "फलाः"
  },
  {
    "question": "का बहुवचन चुनें",
    "word": "फलम्",
    "correctAnswer": "फलानि",
    "wrongAnswer1": "फल",
    "wrongAnswer2": "फलस्य"
  },
  {
    "question": "का बहुवचन चुनें",
    "word": "सुन्दरम्",
    "correctAnswer": "सुन्दरा",
    "wrongAnswer1": "सुन्दरो",
    "wrongAnswer2": "सुन्दराः"
  },

  {
    "question": "का द्विवचन चुनें",
    "word": "फलम्",
    "correctAnswer": "फले",
    "wrongAnswer1": "फलानि",
    "wrongAnswer2": "फलाः"
  },
  {
    "question": "का द्विवचन चुनें",
    "word": "पत्रम्",
    "correctAnswer": "पते",
    "wrongAnswer1": "पत्राणि",
    "wrongAnswer2": "पत्राः"
  },
  {
    "question": "का द्विवचन चुनें",
    "word": "फलम्",
    "correctAnswer": "फले",
    "wrongAnswer1": "फला",
    "wrongAnswer2": "फलं"
  },
  {
    "question": "का द्विवचन चुनें",
    "word": "वृक्षः",
    "correctAnswer": "वृक्षौ",
    "wrongAnswer1": "वृक्षा",
    "wrongAnswer2": "वृक्षा:"
  },
  {
    "question": "का द्विवचन चुनें",
    "word": "फलम्",
    "correctAnswer": "फले",
    "wrongAnswer1": "फलानि",
    "wrongAnswer2": "फलाः"
  }
]
